you have my vote
I need some more armor
how about some armor
help me
I need a handier
behind you
bye
goodbye
clear the area
that was close
get healed here
come here I'll heal you up
come over here if you want healing
laughs
[Music]
in three two one
three two one
special delivery
yeah score one for us
let's attack their flag
get their flag
cover our flag
protect the flag
I'm giving up the flag
dropping the flag
oh come on
that wasn't supposed to happen
someone picked up our flag
they've dropped the flag now's our
chance
we lost our flag
they have our flag get after them
are flags secure
sending the flag back to base
taking the flag back to base
I have the flag
get our flag back
we need to recover the flag
that feels good
now we're in business
keep it coming
oh
my God
that is not okay
damn
fun
no
take out the target
I'm getting good at this
you should sit this one out
don't underestimate me
you're wasting my time
sorry Papa
got you this time Reinhardt
you need to clean up your act
I'll knock some sense into you
had enough
one at a time that's what the old man
says
I've been working on that
I'm more of a cat person
call the blood bank
they're coming right at us
they're behind us
watch the right side
they're above us
up there
they're underneath us
watch your backs
they're right in front of us
on the left
right side
they're on the left
they're below us
what's the doorway
enemy detected
someone sneaking around here
they're over here
one's coming back
there they are
enemies over there
sniper watch out
sniper get behind something
yeah
woohoo
fall back
go
get in there
get out of there
get ready
I'm going in
heading in
group up with me
come over here
everyone group up
rally on the point
I could use some healing
I need healing
oh medic
oh
ah
all patched up
much better
taking my medicine
intense
I needed that
thanks
hey good looking out for me
hey
The Doctor Is In
Brigitte At Your Service
you rang
ITA At Your Service where does it hurt
I will prove myself
please State the nature of your medical
emergency
pushing the attack
I'm going on the attack
I'm on defense
ready to defend
ready
I'm ready
I'll go with you
I'm with you
incoming
they've reached the door
the door is falling apart
get them off the door now
the door is almost destroyed
the doors hanging by a thread
the door's coming down
shock Tire on the left
get them off the door
the Summoner has appeared
the monster is upon us
we need to kill Dr junkenstein
watch out for the reefer
the Witch Is Here
beware the witch still lives
we need to kill the Reaper
we must bring down the monster
slay the Summoner
the doctor still lives
defend our left
the doctor is no more
the reaper haunts us no longer
the monster Falls
the Summoner is banished
the witch is slain
watch all right
shock Tire on the right
defend to the right
watch the bridge
shocked Tire on the bridge
the tire is coming straight for us
it's coming on the left
the door's taking damage
the door is taking damage
and I would fight with you in the next
the hammer is more than just a weapon
only the best ones
why did you come here
is it magic that you do
how fair you Papa
are you searching for a way to return to
the world
what do you make of the countess
what power binds you to this world
foreboding
your weapon looks like a master's work
are all the legends about you true
countess
only when my father's telling stories
your master is a mysterious looking
fellow
are you feeling well you look a little
pale
why do you hide your face
your sword is magnificent
what do you make of the Monk
huh give it time
I'm not sure if Mama would feel the same
how goes your search for the Dragon
looks like I will be watching your back
tonight Papa
always a Critic
how is it you've barely broken a sweat
what was that thing
what brings you here gun singer
never trust a scientist
ah yeah ah yeah ah whoa come on mace to
the face
who wants to party whoa yeah come on
party with me let's go
you're making this easy for me
that's that
[Laughter]
am I moving up in the world
it really makes you think
okay everyone this is it
it all comes down to this
dig deep everyone we can't afford to
lose another
it's win or go home
all we have to do is win another
we're off to a good start
okay here we go
everyone ready let's do this
let's get to work
I could have used a little more time to
get ready
last minute check everyone squared away
don't think we'll be taking a family
vacation here anytime soon Papa might
have a breakdown
I think I'm gonna get tetanus just from
looking at this place
do we have time to go on some rides
flight to duskwood is my favorite
no point in fixing it now you'll
probably just mess it up again
I felt like I had to do more
I knew you'd come around
it's true you have been sacking off a
bit lately
of course how else can I bail you out
when you get into trouble
I've stitched you up so many times it's
a wonder you can still fight
I don't see it that way to me it's an
honor
sure you don't want to sit this one out
Reinhardt
Reinhardt what should I focus on today
Bastian how are you liking that new
armor Papa made for you
Papa what do you think of my armor
Genji how about a quick sparring session
Angela it's so strange to see you in
your armor
I'm really looking forward to fighting
with you pharah
what are you getting at
it'll take some time for me to get
familiar with a design but if you don't
mind I'd love to
you're on
only if we can get something to eat
afterwards
not after how they treated Reinhardt he
deserved better
hey Diva who's your mechanic they do
good work
if I do this wrong it'll hurt a little
if I do it right it'll hurt a lot
ugh
yeah
oh
tiger near
be serious
there's more where that came from
get out of here
we're so close let's get this done
we're almost done hang in there everyone
who's ready to take some punishment
I am Unstoppable
we could use another healer
we need another healer
how about some Shields
I could use some Shields
no
nay
our objectives almost destroyed
we need to keep our defense up
attack the point
I'm planning my flag on the point
I'm taking the objective come on over
we're taking damage
they've broken through
defend the objective
we have to protect the objective
let's take out the objective
destroy the objective
objective eliminated
targets down
we need to sweep them off the point
knock them off the objective
we've damaged the target
that's a good start
the target's almost destroyed
we've almost got it
we need to stop the payload
payload's moving we should put a stop to
that
everyone get on the payload
if we hold them here we win
just a little bit longer and we win this
we need to get things moving
escort the objective
eliminate the objective
we have to eliminate the target
we need to get on the point
everyone group up on the objective
payload is on its way
payload's moving out keep it covered
the payloads under my protection
we need to move the payload
get the payload moving
stop the payload
let's stop that payload
payload stopped is something broken
why is the payload stopped
get that payload moving
we're running out of time
keep the pressure on we can't let up now
focus on the objective
we need to capture the objective
guess I'm gonna have to do this myself
it's all up to me
I'm On Fire come on try me
it's automatic
maybe you should just stay out of my way
on my way
be right there
oh
we need to press the attack
keep moving forward
push forward
feels like I'm forgetting something
you looked like you needed a hand
I'm keeping an eye on you
this is all part of the learning process
I can do better than that
this is not the end of the world
this might need a few adjustments
back to the drawing board
that wasn't the plan
ready for more
practice makes perfect not to mention
some bumps and bruises
no place to go but up
back in the fight
where does it hurt
things were going so well
thanks Angela
ready for another round
assassins disappeared
assassins out of the picture
there's an assassin here
assessors on me
get her off me
watch out for the Assassin
we have to do something about that
assassin
assassins on you watch out
telem forces incoming
watch out more Talent on the way
heads up
Talent forces incoming
they're dropping down from above
heads up they're above us
reinforcements coming in on that boat
what's that boat
they're coming through the door
watch that door
drop ship flying in
Dropship incoming
watch out for that Dropship
watch the window
they're coming through the window
and force us out of commission
enforcers out of commission
enforce her incoming
someone take out the enforcer
heavy assault units been damaged
Heavies down
look out heavy assault unit
we have to do something about the heavy
I took out the sniper
they deployed a sniper
someone deal with that sniper already
look out snipers on you
enforcer spotted
sniper look out
Talon Troopers coming for us
I didn't forget about you
be careful who you mess with
what I get
huh
oh
let's set up here
they're using a shield generator
enemy Shield generator destroyed
found their Shield generator
that's my fault
sorry about that
oh
take cover
nice one
we got this
I always had faith in you
you've been practicing
that's the last of them
claw
we have a teammate down
our teammates down
things just get a little more difficult
watch yourselves out there
don't mess around
I'm over here
over here
find their teleporter
they have a teleporter somewhere
enemy teleporter out of commission
the teleporters over here
thanks
thank you
touch
we're almost out of time
if we're gonna do this the time is now
enemy turret destroyed
sorry Papa back to the scrap peep
enemy turret ahead
enemy turret ahead one of Papa's beloved
creations
My ultimate is almost ready
My ultimate is charging
My ultimate is ready come on
rally to me
I'm ready to Rally
My ultimate is ready
I'm under Fire
taking heavy fire
help me
I'm taking damage
they're on me
I'm under attack
got it
understood
I'm on it
come on everyone
get in
that's how you do it
I'll lead the way
follow me
come here
Shields holding
Shields taking damage
my barrier can't take much more
my barrier's about to go
my barrier's down
get back
turning defense into offense
step off
you might want to keep your distance
the best offense is a good defense
oh looks like that hurt next
I meant to do that
see ya
beginner's luck
farewell
practice makes perfect
yet
oh
get behind me
I will shield you
I've got you covered
my Shield's up
you're taking it
foreign
you'll feel better soon
fixing you up
that should be better
I'll take care of you
patching you up
I've got you
do more Beth does not
my turn to take care of you Angela
patching you up Reinhardt
Let Me patch that up
I've got you Papa
feeling better
good as new
yeah
sterilizing now
I'll get you fixed right up
get in there
armoring you up
take some armor
giving you a little extra
toilet decreed
I'll get you fixed right up
I've got a present for you
bought from me
I see you over there
bet you didn't see that coming
patience prognosis is dead
I am
I will be your Shield
a tiger can't change its stripes
no sweat
something doesn't feel right
not feeling so good
feeling sluggish here
Detonator destroyed
Detonator incoming
enemy Bastion eliminated
enemy Bastion engaging
Eradicator scrap
eradicate her up ahead
that's it for those null Troopers
null Troopers here
the or-14 is destroyed
be careful or 14.
I really need some healing
I need healing right away
revive me
get me back in the fight
back on your feet
let's finish this fight together
slicer's taken care of
slicers incoming
you won't be disappointed
you're not scared are you
mace to the face
and
go you
outside the gold
on
ion
foreign
it's just a flesh wound
time to roll up my sleeves
what do you think you're doing
no shortcuts just hard work
be reasonable
someone has to be the voice of reason
leave this to an expert
hard work pays off
trust me
Precision Swedish engineering
Scandinavian Style no it has to be
leaned home style
was that supposed to scare me
who's ready to party
I made that just for you
love me so my
oh thanks everyone
now that's a vote of confidence
just doing my part
operation complete now where did I leave
my watch
can't argue with that
glad we're all in agreement
that's a serious outbreak
yes
y'all
you're welcome
it was nothing
so
your armor seems to be working well I
guess you were right about the core
integration design
I knew you'd come around
stay close to me
of course how else can I bail you out
when you get into trouble
I'm really looking forward to fighting
with you pharah
we OverWatch brats have to stick
together
Papa what do you think of my armor
not bad not bad I'm glad you let me add
a little something to it
Angela it's so strange to see you in
your armor
I could say the same for you
Reinhardt what should I focus on today
try to keep me out of trouble
protect your teammates make sure they do
not falter
focus on offense drive your enemy back
with the blows from your flail
your Shield keep yourself from harm they
bear against our enemies
no lesson today show me what you have
learned
believe me I get wanted to wear the
armor and all but following the old man
around must be nothing but trouble
I don't see it that way to me it's an
honor
I've stitched you up so many times it's
a wonder you can still fight
just some bumps and bruises nothing to
worry yourself
looks like I will be watching your back
tonight Papa
it's good to fight alongside someone I
know I can trust
your master is a mysterious looking
fellow
I have learned much from him
a little about him
you're better than me in a fight I grant
you that but I still have the edge on
you in smithing
huh give it time
how goes your search for the Dragon
I farted once or twice and have been
lucky only to lose what I have
I'm not sure if Mama would feel the same
I'm still quite handsome
what do you make of the Monk
I do not trust him any strange gods
your sword is magnificent
it is one of the legendary plays of my
family
[Music]
how is it you've barely broken a sweat
it must be my many years of training
careful diet and simple way of life
is it magic that you do
it is not magic but the power of the
spirit that I Channel
why did you come here
I am following in my Master's footsteps
searching for enlightenment though my
path has not always been a straight one
mind your defense the battle is far from
over
always a Critic
my elbow Servo isn't actuating God it's
annoying
[Applause]
no point in fixing it now you'll
probably just mess it up again
hey brigitta want to go hit the weights
you're on
only if we can get something to eat
afterwards
did you ever want to join OverWatch
growing up
not after how they treated Reinhardt he
deserved better
isn't it enough to be an engineer
brigitta
I felt like I had to do more
why does everyone keep pestering me
about my aardvarks
it's true you have been sucking off a
bit lately
hey Diva who's your mechanic they do
good work
he's great isn't he
sure you don't want to sit this one out
Reinhardt
you ask that every time and every time I
say no today is no different
how are you liking that new armor Papa
made for you
Genji how about a quick sparring session
Johan show me what you've been working
on
you know I've seen reinhardt's OverWatch
file
what are you getting at
I wonder if he's really told you the
truth about his retirement
why do you hide your face
so The Others May look upon me without
fear or pity
are you feeling well you look a little
pale
I stay out of the Sun
are all the legends about you true
countess
don't believe everything you've heard
your weapon looks like a master's work
it was its Creator's finest piece
crafted just before his demise
foreboding
what power binds you to this world
a magical catastrophe that told my
spirit from my body
what do you make of the countess
I do not trust her at all
are you searching for a way to return to
the world
once perhaps but now I am at peace
how fair you Papa
I can handle myself mind your own battle
what was that thing
a man who felt a shadow
are all the Warriors of your land women
only the best ones
were these stronger the hammer or the
sword
the hammer is more than just a weapon
in my former life I would have gladly
fought by your side
and I would fight with you in the next
I'd love it if you could take a look at
my armor sometime
it'll take some time for me to get
familiar with the design but if you
don't mind I'd love to
have you ever faced a dragon
only when my father's telling stories
what do you make of this Dr junkenstein
never trust a scientist
what brings you here Gunslinger
people hire me to hunt monsters
werewolves vampires witches talkative
scientists
[Music]
thank you